http://www.heil-law.com/privacy-policy/

HomeAboutFree ConsultationPractice AreasAuto AccidentBicycle AccidentsBed BugsBoating AccidentsBrain InjuryBurn InjuryDefective ProductDog BitesEpcot InjuryHomeowner’s CasesHurricane Irma ClaimsHurricane Matthew ClaimsInsurance ClaimLegal ConsultationsBus AccidentsMedical MalpracticeMotorcycle AccidentsNeck and BackNursing Home NeglectPedestrian AccidentsPharmacy NegligencePool AccidentScooter InjuriesSexual HarassmentSlip & FallSpider BitesTrucking AccidentsTheme Park AccidentWalt Disney World InjuriesWorkers’ CompensationResultsFAQContact MePrivacy Policy for David R. Heil, P.A.At www.heil-law.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by www.heil-law.com and how we use it.If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at david@heil-law.com.Log Fileswww.heil-law.com follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.Privacy PoliciesYou may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of www.heil-law.com.Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on www.heil-law.com, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.Note that www.heil-law.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.Third Part Privacy Policieswww.heil-law.com’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?Children’s InformationAnother part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.www.heil-law.com does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in www.heil-law.com. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.ConsentBy using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
Share on Facebook Share
Share on TwitterTweet
Share on Pinterest Share
Share on LinkedIn Share
Share on Digg Share Contact MeCall for a FREE CONSULTATION 24x7: (800) 952-1622Winter Park: (407) 599-2100 |
DeLand: (386) 736-9000 |
Melbourne: (321) 327-2944 | Orlando:(407) 326-2517Practice AreasAuto AccidentsBicycle AccidentsBoating AccidentsBrain InjuriesBurn CasesDefective ProductsDog BitesEpcot InjuriesFree Legal ConsultationHomeowner’s CasesInsurance Claim DisputesLynx Bus AccidentsMedical MalpracticeMotorcycle AccidentsNeck & Back InjuriesNursing Home NeglectPedestrian AccidentsPharmacy NegligencePool AccidentsSexual HarassmentSlip & Fall InjuriesTheme Park AccidentsWalt Disney World InjuriesWorkers CompensationDavid R. Heil P.A.I am a trial attorney with over 35 years of experience in civil trial law. Your case will not be handled by an investigator, paralegal or case manager. I will personally meet with you to discuss your case at one of my offices, the hospital or your home. Legal information is available.Request a FREE CASE REVIEWFirst Name:*Last Name:*Email* Phone #*Case Details*CAPTCHAEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Why Choose David R. Heil, PA?No Fee Unless We Win35+ Years of ExperienceFree Consultation Recent Blog Entries What to Know About Dog Bite Cases Do You Need a local Lawyer for a Florida Insurance Claim? What Happens During a Legal Consultation? What Documents Do You Need for a Personal Injury Claim? How to report nursing home neglect?Quick LinksAbout David R. HeilCase ResultsContact Our FirmFAQFREE CONSULTATIONMy BlogOffice LocationsPractice AreasTestimonialsMy YouTube ChannelDavid R. Heil, PA - Better Business Bureau A+ Rated - Office LocationsWinter Park - 2324 Lee Road Winter Park, FL 32789 Phone: (407) 599-2100Melbourne - 1900 S Harbor City Blvd, Suite 219, Melbourne, Florida 32901 Phone: (321) 327-2944Orlando - 121 S Orange Ave Suite 1596, Orlando, FL 32801 Phone: (407) 326-2517Areas Served in Central FloridaApopkaAltamonte SpringsBrevardCasselberryCentral FloridaClermontCocoa BeachDaytona BeachDeBaryDeLandDeltonaEast OrlandoFloridaLake Buena VistaLake MaryLongwoodMalabarMelbourneMerritt IslandNew Smyrna BeachOrange CityOrlandoPalm BayRockledgeSanfordSatellite BeachSpace CoastTitusvilleVieraWinter ParkWinter SpringsImportant NoteThe hiring of a personal injury lawyer is an important decision and should not be based solely upon advertisements. Before you decide, ask me to send you free written information about my qualifications and experience.This web site is designed for general information only. The information presented at this site should not be construed to be formal legal advice nor the formation of a lawyer/client relationship.Similar successful monetary results may not be seen by all clients seeking representation from Heil Law for accident or injury claims as each case is different. These results also reflect amounts awarded prior to deductions for attorney's fees, medical bills, and other court costs.Copyright © 2020 David R. Heil, PA – Injury Attorney - Terms of Use - Privacy Policy - Accessibility Policy -  SitemapDesign and Marketing by Orange Rock Media
